Wanfei (Felicia) Luo

Tel: 732-532-9054 Email: luowanfei@gmail.com Website: https://felicia1017.github.io/#home

SUMMARY: Highly motivated, adaptable graduate student in Data Analytics with strong knowledge of analytical languages, such as Python, R, and SQL, and hands-on experiences with AWS services, BusinessObjects, Oracle Database, Power BI and Tableau at work.

EDUCATION:

Master of Business and Science Rutgers University, New Brunswick NJ Graduation: May 2020

• Concentration: Data Analytics

Bachelor of Arts Rutgers University, New Brunswick NJ Graduation: May 2018

Major: EconomicsMinor: Statistics

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE & PROJECT

Next Gen Data Analyst Intern Legg Mason, NYC, NY May 2019 to June 2020

American investment management firm with a focus on worldwide asset management services.

- Work with the IT data team to build AWS Redshift-based enterprise database system and integrate external data and internal data for improving pipeline operations.
- Design and develop new managerial dashboards on Tableau by querying internal and competitive data from enterprise database and external sources to uncover potential growth opportunities in new products or businesses.
- Work on various ad hoc diagnostic and descriptive analytics, and programming assignments using Python.
- Perform monthly and quarterly reports on competitive pricing analysis using SAP BusinessObjects and excel for the US product team and fund board members.

Data Analyst Externship Becton Dickinson, Franklin Lake, NJ Sep 2018 to Feb 2019 Leading global provider of pharmaceutical devices and technology solutions.

- Research, design and implement predictive models and natural language processing techniques to help spot anomalous transactions using R.
- Collaborate with the internal auditing team to develop solutions for complex internal management and internal audits.
- Design, develop and implement anomalous detection of T&E (Travel and Expenses) transactions by analyzing large structured and unstructured datasets.

Market Development Intern CDV Haimi Culture Media Co., China June to Aug 2016 New media firm, providing virtual advertisement solutions into real-time television services.

- Perform an exploratory analysis of millions of expense reporting records using excel.
- Design product presentation slides for B2B commercial promotional purposes.
- Conduct research on advertising data for identifying topics that the audience and advertisers interested in.

ACHIEVEMENTS / CERTIFICATIONS:

- Treasurer, MBS student organization Jan 2019 to now
- MBS Fellowship 2020 academic year
- National Swimming Championship 2011-2012 (China) silver medal in women's 100-meter butterfly